<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="Koko_Head_Milestone">
        <item>
            This hike is a relatively straightforward as you will be climbing up railroad tracks.
            However this hike requires good physical condition as the heat and 1000 steps make this
            tough. The uneven terrain also can prove to be challenging so be sure to wear proper
            gear.
            \n\n Please be aware of any posted signage and read warnings carefully.
    </item>
        <item>
            Simply hike up the stairs until you reach the outpost at the top. Please be mindful
            of others climbing down the steps. To get back, walk back down the steps to the start
            of the trail.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <integer-array name="Koko_Head_Milestone_Images">
        <item>@drawable/milestone_koko1</item>
        <item>@drawable/milestone_koko2</item>
    </integer-array>


    <string-array name="Manoa_Falls_Milestone">
        <item>
                    The gate to the trail will be near the message board.
            \n\n    Your start and return point will be here so backtracking will be needed.
                    Take care to observe the posted messages and familiarize yourself with the signage.
        </item>
        <item>
                    The second area to look for is in the wooden planks. This crosses over a stream.
            \n\n    Continue to follow the worn path to avoid injuries and erosion to other areas of the trail.
        </item>
        <item>
                    There will be an opening in the canopy with two paths. There are multiple ways to
                    continue up but be sure to account for the mud here. The incline becomes very steep
                    and may prove difficult on rainy days.
            \n\n    Walk until you reach the stone walls
        </item>
        <item>
                    You should reach an area with many roots coming out of the ground.
                    In addition there will be plastic footings here to help with grip. The terrain
                    after this point becomes muddier and elevates.
            \n\n    Continue on until you reach a large opening
        </item>
        <item>
                    Approach these stairs with caution and be mindful of others. There are no handrails
                    and can be slippery if damp.
            \n\n    Continue on until you see the waterfall
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <integer-array name="Manoa_Falls_Milestone_Images">
        <item>@drawable/milestone_manoa1</item>
        <item>@drawable/milestone_manoa2</item>
        <item>@drawable/milestone_manoa3</item>
        <item>@drawable/milestone_manoa4</item>
        <item>@drawable/milestone_manoa5</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_manoa_falls</item>
    </integer-array>


    <string-array name="Makapuu_Lighthouse_Milestone">
        <item>
                    The entrance for this trail is marked clearly by some bollards after the end of the
                    parking lot. Take care to read the posted signage and understand the safety warnings.
          \n\n      There will be a smooth asphalt walkway that curves up to the 2nd milestone. Since
                    the path is very clearly marked, do not go off the white lines to avoid eroding
                    surroundings.
        </item>
        <item>
                    The second milestone will have the lighthouse visibly around the corner. As you
                    walk up there will be a fork in the road. Walk to the right to get to a vantage point.
                    otherwise take the left or turn around to get to the start.
            \n\n    Continue until you reach the edge of the lookout
        </item>
        <item>
                    The lighthouse will be below the cliff. Take the time to rest here.
            \n\n    Backtrack to the start of the trail on the same path taken earlier.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <integer-array name="Makapuu_Lighthouse_Milestone_Images">
        <item>@drawable/milestone_lighthouse1</item>
        <item>@drawable/milestone_lighthouse2</item>
        <item>@drawable/milestone_lighthouse3</item>
    </integer-array>


    <string-array name="Lanikai_Pillboxes_Milestone">
        <item>The start of the Lanikai ridge trail is marked with a manmade sign and is between 2 areas of private property, the trail quickly gets steep as you ascend the mountain ridge!</item>
        <item>The ridge is easy to follow without any confusing paths, keep following it until you reach the first pillbox.</item>
        <item>Continue along the ridge until you reach the next pillbox.</item>
        <item>The final pillbox is much smaller and eroded but marks the end of the hike.</item>>
    </string-array>
    <integer-array name="Lanikai_Pillboxes_Milestone_Images">
        <item>@drawable/milestone_lanikai1</item>
        <item>@drawable/milestone_lanikai2</item>
        <item>@drawable/milestone_lanikai3</item>
        <item>@drawable/milestone_lanikai4</item>
    </integer-array>


    <string-array name="Maunawili_Falls_Milestone">
        <item>The start of the Maunawili trail is marked by handmade posted sign with a clear path, follow this path for the first 2 miles.</item>
        <item>You\'ll come to a bend in the path with staircases going to the left, descend these stairs to get to the river floor.</item>
        <item>Once at the bottom of the valley follow the river upstream until you get to the waterfall.</item>
    </string-array>
    <integer-array name="Maunawili_Falls_Milestone_Images">
        <item>@drawable/milestone_maunawili1</item>
        <item>@drawable/milestone_maunawili2</item>
        <item>@drawable/milestone_maunawili3</item>
    </integer-array>


    <string-array name="Stairway_to_Heaven_Milestone">
        <item>The legal route to the Stairway to Heaven starts with the Moanalua valley trail, marked by a state hike marker and green vehicle gate.</item>
        <item>The Moanalua valley trail is a scenic forest semi-paved trail with 17 small bridge and water passings, be careful during rainy seasons as these passings may be flooded.</item>
        <item>At the end of the Moanalua trail there will be a state marked sign, turn left at the sign and follow the small uphill path.  This will start to take you up the mountain ridge.</item>
        <item>Continue hiking up the steep mountain range until you reach the very top, certain sections of the ridge are very steep and have rope railings you can use to climb up.</item>
        <item>Once you reach the satellite tower you will be at the top of the Stairway to Heaven.  You can climb down these stairs partway for pictures but do not descend all the way as this will take you to the illegal entrance.  You must go back the way you came.</item>
    </string-array>
    <integer-array name="Stairway_to_Heaven_Milestone_Images">
        <item>@drawable/milestone_stairway1</item>
        <item>@drawable/milestone_stairway2</item>>
        <item>@drawable/milestone_stairway3</item>
        <item>@drawable/milestone_stairway4</item>
        <item>@drawable/milestone_stairway5</item>
    </integer-array>

</resources>